JUHYOUNG LEE studiopeca.lee@gmail.com +81)70-4295-5352 https://pecalee.github.io

Education

Tokyo Filmcenter College of Arts Design /2020

tokyo.Japan

Seoul National University

Visual design /2015 dropped out

seoul.Korea

Skills

web interface design graphic design visual design motion design

Main tools

illustrator photoshop premiere pro after effects Adobe Xd figma Html css Javascript

python

Language

Korean
Japanese
English(little bit)

Interest

video game photography videography skateboarding

Professional profile

I'm a Tokyo resident designer who works mainly in web design and graphic design. Researching current trends and specializing in visual programming and interaction. Designing the most effective digital assets

from a limited budget by utilizing brand identity.

Designing in a wide range of areas including motion graphics.

Utilizing my Korean, Japanese and English language skills to create various designs in different languages as well as catering to different cultures.

Experience

CS-C Co., Ltd. | tokyo.japan

04.2020 - present

Marketing company.

Worked as a graphic and web designer.

Designing digital assets for advertisement to match brand's identity and target.

Working closely with project managers to determine the direction of our design based on user research and feedback from clients for the projects.

- graphic design asset design print design UI prototyping creative planning
- Designing responsive website of National BBQ brand.
- Developing digital promotions, icons and web banners for web advertisements.
- · Created promotional videos for both online and online use.

Freelance designer | seoul.korea, tokyo.japan

04 2015 - 03 2020

Worked as a freelancer.

Provided service to my clients by designing logos, icons, landing pages, pamphlets and web contents.

- · graphic design · asset design · print design · web page design · motion design
- Designing logotype for web marketing tool "C-mo".
- · Created opening sequence for mobile game that called "retrieve".
- Refreshing BI for "LIGHT UP COMPANY"
- $\cdot \text{ Created opening video for 2018 the end of the year concert of J-rock band who called "jealkb"}.$
- Created web contents for Seven "Big Sisters".
- Designing and coding website of Herald foreign language institute.

VCNC | seoul.korea

03.2014 - 12.2014

Startup company that developed a couple messenger called between.

Worked as a graphic designer.

I produced digital assets of product for Japanese market.

• graphic design • asset design • creative planning

Freelance designer | seoul.korea

2011 - 02.2014

Worked as a freelancer and work for various clients.

Provided service to my clients by designing logos, icons, landing pages, and pamphlets.

- graphic design
 asset design
 web design
- Designing korean traditional musical instrument app "Pyungyung".
- Created web season book for elog that was korean fast fashion brand.